Allan Marquand Papers, 1858-1951 (bulk 1878-1950): Finding Aid C0269
Manuscripts Division
- Series 2: Correspondence, 1872-1924; 1950-1951; 9 boxes
  - The American Federation of Arts, 1909-1912; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - American Literary Bureau, 1874; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Andrews, T. J, 1886; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Andrews, William S. (1847-1929), 1874; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Antinori, P, 1908; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Archaeological Institute of America, 1909-1924; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Art Salon Universal, 1918; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Ashbee, Charles Robert (1863-1942), 1922-1923; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Ashmolean Museum--Oxford Department of Fine Art, 1910; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Ashmore, Irving G, 1909; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Astor, William Waldorf (1848-1919), 1877; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Atherton, Thomas H, 1877; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Atwater, Addison, 1876; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Atwater, L. H. (1813-1883), 1878; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - "Bache", 1911; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Baddely, St. Clair, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Baker, William M. (1825-1883), 1876; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Ballard, Harlan Hogue (1853-1934), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Baltimore Cricket Club, 1879; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Bancroft T. Whiting, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Bardini, Stefano, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Baumann Brothers, 1887; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Bayerisches National Museum, 1913; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Beazley, John Davidson (1885-1970), 1911; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Beecher, Henry Ward (1813-1887), 1874; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Benda, G, 1910; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Benjamin, S. G. W. (1837-1914), 1887; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Berenson, Bernhard (1865-1959), 1911; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Bigelow, Poultney (1855-1954), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Blackgield, E. H, 1904; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Blecker, C, 1887; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Bleoniwell, H. B, 1876; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Bloch, Emil, 1910; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Bode, Wilhelm von (1845-1929), 1896-1922; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Bonaventure, E. F, 1912; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Bosanquet, R. C, 1909; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Bossange, E. Raymond (1871-1947), 1923; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Boston Museum of Fine Arts, 1918; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Boughton, G. H. (1833-1905), 1888-1893; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Bowman A. A, 1912-1913; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Boyce, L, 1872; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Boyd, C. W, 1879; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Boyesen, Hjalmar Hjorth (1848-1895), 1893-1894; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Brackett, Mrs., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Bradley, Edson, 1912; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Bridge, J. Howard (1856-1939), 1918; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Briggs, Henry C, 1900; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Brinton, Christian (1870-1942), 1915; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - British Museum--Dept. of Coins & Medals, 1913; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Brockhaus, Heinrich (1858-1941), 1909; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Brown, Alice Van Vechton (1862-1949), 1910; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Browne, Hugh M, 1876; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Brownlow, Lord, 1918; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Bruckett, C. F, 1876; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Bryan, J. P. Kennedy (1852- ), 1875-1896; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Bryce, James, 1904; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Bulloz, J. E, 1913; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Bullow, Grafin von, 1910; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Burke, Robert E, 1922; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Burlamacchi, Lucy, 1900; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Burlington Magazine, 1902; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Burt, Horace B, 1873; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Burton, Henry H, 1908-1921; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Butler, Howard Crosby (1872-1922), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Butler, Mary M, 1878; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Canessa Gallery, 1917; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Cannon, Henry White (1850-1934), 1909; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Carey, Francis K, 1880; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Carlisle, Mildred, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Carpenter, William L, 1887; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Carter, Ernest, 1902; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Carter, Jesse Benedict (1872-1917), 1909; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Catini, A, 1902; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Caulfield, Edward B, 1901; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Cellere, di, F, 1917; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - The Century Association, 1887; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Cerimbole, C, 1897; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Cermont, F, 1913; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 12a.)
  - Cesnola, Luigi Palmadi Di (1832-1904), 1902; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Charles, B. A, 1918; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Chase, George Henry (1874-1952), 1922; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 15)
    TLS (copy) by Paul di Sachs to Chase
  - Choisy, Francois Auguste (1841-1909), 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Clark, Charles Upson (1875-1960), 1912-1922; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Clarke, Thomas B. (1848-1931), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Clarke, Thomas Shields (1860-1920), 1909; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Clayton, John R, 1911; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - The Cleveland Museum of Art, 1922; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 21)
    William M. Milliken, TLS
  - Cleveland, Frances Folsom (1864-1947), 1888-1890; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Coit, Henry Augustus (1830-1895), 1872-1879; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - College Art Association, 1913; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - College of New Jersey Preparatory School, 1876; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Collignoy, M, 1907; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Congresso Internazionale di Storia dell'Arte, 1912; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Conkling, Paul B, 1893; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Conway, William Martin, 1st Baron of Allington (1856-1937), 1905; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Cook, Walter, W. S, 1924; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Cooke, Josiah Parsons (1827-1894), 1886; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Coon, Spencer H, 1877; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Cornelius, Charles Over (1890-1937), 1921; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Cornwall, H. B, 1876; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Coube, A, 1911; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Coubertin, Pierre de (1863-1937), 1924; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Courtney, Henry N, 1876; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Cowen, John Kissig (1844-1904), 1876; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Crawford, F. Marion (1854-1909), 1907; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Crawford, Mary Caroline (1874-1932), 1912; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Crosby, Ernest Howard (1856-1907), 1876; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Cross, J. M, 1876-1877; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Cross, John W, 1922; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Cruttwell, Maud, 1901-1913; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Curtis, Allen, 1882; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - The Daily Princetonian, 1911; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Da Porto, Giusseppi, 1918; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Davis, John D. (1854-1926), 1872-1875; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Davis, Thomas, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - De Forest, Robert Weeks (1848-1931), 1911; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Deer, Louis, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Dennis, Martin, 1876; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Diehl, Conrad (1843- ), 1912; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Dimeau, Louis, 1893; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Dirssen, Von, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Dix, William Frederic (1867-1945), 1887-1888; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Dod, S. B, 1876; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Dodge, Mr., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Dorner, D., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Dorpfield, Wilhelm (1853-1940), 1903; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Douglas, Robert Langton (1864-1951), 1911; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Duffield, John T. (1823-1901), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Durell, F., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Durlacher Bros, 1916; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Eames, Emma (1865-1952), 1886-1887; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Eames, Emma Haydon, 1886-1887; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Edgell, George Harold (1887-1954), 1912; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Edmonds, W. L, 1876; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Edmonds, Walter D. (1851- ), 1875-1879; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Edwards, Amelia Ann B. (1831-1892), 1888; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Egypt Exploration Fund, 1909; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Elder, F. R. (1885-1962), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Elderkin, George W. (1879-1965), 1922; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Eliot, Charles W. (1834-1926), 1894; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Ellsworth, James W. (1849-1925), 1912; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Emerson, Alfred (1859- ), 1893; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Evans, Sir Arthur John (1851-1941), 1800s; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Farnham(?), Henry, 1902; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Farr, James M, 1895; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Farrand, Wilson (1862-1942), 1910; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Farrell, Arthur, 1902; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Ferree, Barr (d. 1924), 1909; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Fields, James Thomas (1817-1881), 1873-1874; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Figdor, A, 1910; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Figueirnedo, José de, 1908-1922; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Fine, May Margaret (1869- ), 1924; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Fiske, John (1842-1901), 1893; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Fiske, Willard (1831-1904), 1893-1902; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Flanagan, John (1865?-1952), 1923; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Fletcher, Frederick, W, 1921; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Fowler, Harold North (1859-1955), 1909; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Frayer, Eugene, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Frazer, Sir James George (1854-1941), 1909; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Frothingham, Arthur Lincoln (1859-1923), 1886; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Frullini, Luigi, 1894; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Fry, Roger (1866-1934), 1912; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Fuller-Maitland, W, 1911; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Gadow, Hans Friedrich (1855-1928), 1902; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Gardner, Ernest Arthur (1862-1939), 1904; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Gardner, Isabella Stewart (1840-1924), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Gardner, Percy (1846-1937), 1911; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Garfield, Harry Augustus (1863-1942), 1911; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Garrett, Robert (1875-1961), 1901; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Gentner, Philip J, 1912; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Gerould, James T. (1872-1951), 1924; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Gilman, Benj. I. (1852-1933), 1880-1918; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Gilmore & Gibson, 1880; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Giraud, Carlo M, 1916; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Glück, G, 1913; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Glyde, Edmund M, 1900; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Godwin, Frederick, 1922; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Godwin, Harold (1857-1931), 1879; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Godwin, Parke (1816-1904), 1876; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Goldie, George, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Goodnight, S. H. (1875-1972), 1912; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Goodnow, Sara Whitney, 1902; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Gordon, William S, 1876; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Gosse, Sir Edmund Wilson (1849-1928), 1885; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Green, Elmer E, 1876; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Greene, Richard A, 1879; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Greene, William Brenton, Jr. (1854-1928), 1876-1877; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Greenlee, Wendell W, 1920; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Grolier Club, 1888; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Gronau, Georg, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Guillaumier, P, 1913; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Gulick, Mrs. I. L., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Gnoli, Umberto, 1917; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Guyot, Arnold Henry (1807-1884), 1876; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Hackett, Mary E., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Hadley, Arthur Twining (1856-1930), 1879-1922; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Hall, Alfred L, 1902; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Hall, G. Stanley (1844-1924), 1886; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Hall, J. Dewitt, 1873; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Hall, John, 1871-1875; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Hall, Robert, 1872-1874; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Halsted, George Brude (1853-1922), 1886; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Hamlin, Alfred Dwight (1855-1926), 1906-1909; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Harland, J. Penrose (1891-1923), 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Harriman, Mrs., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Harris, William, 1876; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Harris, William Torrey (1835-1909_, 1896; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Harrison, Hall (1837-1900), 1874; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Hart, John Seeley (1810-1877), 1876; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Harvey, Thomas W, 1875; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Haseltine, J. P, 1921; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Haussoulier, Bernard, 1909; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Hawes, George (1864- ), 1900; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - Hawthorne, Julian (1846-1934), 1900; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - Helbig, Wolfgang (1839-1915), 1888-1889; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Henry, J. Bayard, 1893; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - Hepworth, George Hughes(1833-1902), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - Hibben, John Grier (1861-1933), 1912-1922; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - Hiersemann, Karl W, 1886; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - Higginson, Thomas Wentworth Storrow (1823-1911), 1874-1876; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Hill, B. H, 1922; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - Hilprecht, Hermann V. Volrath (1859-1925), 1893; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - Hindley & Wilkerson, Ltd, 1911; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - Hitchcock, Roswell Dwight (1817-1887), 1877; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - Hogarth, David George (1862-1927), 1908-1911; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Holden, Edward Singleton (1846-1914), 1913; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Horne, Herbert P, 1916; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Huguenot Society of America, 1898-1902; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Hulfish, [?], 1911; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Hun, [J?], dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Hunt, Catherine C, 1886; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Hunt, Edith Holman, 1911; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Huss, H, 1893; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Hutton, Laurence (1843-1904), 1902; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Hyde, William DeWitt (1858-1917), 1911; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Hymans, Henri Simon (1836-1912), 1903; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Ichenhauswer, J. D, 1902; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - J. & S. Goldschmidt, 1910; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Jaccaci, August F, 1912; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Jackson, Schuyler B. (1849-1914), 1911; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Jacobus, M. W. (1855-1937), 1876; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - James R. Osgood & Co. Publishers, 1876; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - James, William (1842-1910), 1902-1906; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Janssen, Pierre Jules Cesar (1824-1907), 1896; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Jenney, A. C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Jessup, Henry W. (1864-1934), 1895; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Jevons, William Stanley (1835-1882), 1881; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Johns Hopkins Alumni Assn, 1887; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Johns Hopkins University, 1909; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Johnson, John G. (1841-1917), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Johonnot, James (1823-1888), 1885-1886; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Joline, Mrs. C. A., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Kalen, Addie C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Kaneko, Baron Kentaro, 1905; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Kelly, George F., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Kelly, Thomas Hughes, 1912; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Kelsey, Francis Willey (1858-1927), 1895; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Kemp, S. G., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Kendall, William Sergeant (1869-1938), 1920; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Kennedy, Clarence (1892-1972), 1922; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 36)
    "Italian Epigraphy"
  - Kimball, R. B., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Knox, Henry (Harry) C, 1868-1870; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Koch, Guenther, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Koldewey, Robert (1855-1925), 1910; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Lafand, P, 1911; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - LaFarge, John (1835-1910), 1909; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Lafrenestre, Georges (1837-1919), 1907-1908; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Lamborn, Robert H, 1884-1885; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Lanciani, Rudolfo Amadeo (1846-1929), 1893; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Lathrop, Francis Augustus (1849-1909), 1903-1907; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Lechat, Henri, 1909; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Lee, Sir Sidney (1859-1926), 1902; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Leighton, Frederick, Baron Leighton of Stretton (1830-1896), 1887-1889; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Lelli, Giuseppe, 1908; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Lemard, T. D., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - "Lemmonier", 1920; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Lepke, Rudolph, 1910; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Lethaby, W. R, 1911; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Levi, Eugenia, 1914; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Libbey, Jonas Marsh (1857-1922), 1878-1880; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Libbey, William (1855-1927), 1876; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Library Bureau, 1902; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Likhatscheff, Nicolas, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Limite, L. Richmond, 1876; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Littman, Enno (1875-1956), 1902; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Lombardi, J, 1897; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Lounsbery & Co. [Philip M. Lydig], 1911; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Maclagan, Eric, 1915-1919; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Macleash, W, 1903; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - The Macmillan Company (George P. Brett), 1909; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - MacMonnies, Frederick (1863-1937), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - The Manchester Whitworth Institute, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Manifattura di Signa, 1918; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Marquand, Eleanor Cross (wife) (1896-1903), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Including several miscellaneous letters to Mrs. Marquand
  - Marquand, Elizabeth (sister), 1877-1878; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Marquand, Elizabeth Love (Allen) (mother), 1875-1892; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Marquand, Frederick (uncle), 1877-1878; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Marquand, Frederick A. (brother), 1875-1879; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Marquand, Henry (brother), 1875-1878; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Marquand, Henry Gurdon (father) (1819-1902), 1875-1892; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Marquand, Linda (sister), 1875-1877; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Marquand Mabel (sister), 1875-1892; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Marquand, Eleanor (Mrs. Douglas Delanoy) (daughter), 1908; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Marquand, Elizabeth (sister), 1871-1878; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Marquand, Elizabeth Love (Allen) (mother), 1868-1880; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 18)
    Including correspondence to brothers Henry and Frederick
  - Marquand, Frederick A. (brother) (1875-1879), 1873-1881; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Marquand, Henry (brother), 1868-1911; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Marquand, Henry Gurdon (father) (1819-1902), 1868-1879; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 21)
    Including letters to brother Frederick
  - Marquand, Linda (sister), 1873-1881; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Marquand, Mabel (sister), 1871-1875; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - "Aunt Mary", 1892; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Marshall, Henry Rutgers (1852-1927), 1918; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Marsianno, Rocchi, 1902; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - The Maryland Club, 1878; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Mather, Frank Jewett (1868-1953), 1910-1922; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Mather, Rufus Graves (1874-1952), 1913-1920; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Maury, Richard L., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Mayer & Müller, 1897; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - McCauley, H. B., Jr, 1876-1880; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - McClenahan, Howard (1872-1935), 1922; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - McClintock, Gilbert S. (1886- ), 1922; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - McClure, Alexander D, 1874; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - McCormick, Cyrus Hall (1859-1936), 1923; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - McCormick, Cyrus Hall (1890-1970), 1923; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - McCosh, Isabella, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - McCosh, James (1811-1894), 1871-1894; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - McDonald, H. M, 1876; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - McIlvain, J. Willie, 1874-1876; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - McIvlaine, H, 1876; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - McKecknie, J. W, 1895; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - McKee, Joseph, 1918; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - McPherson, S. J, 1877; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - McWhood, Leonard B, 1910; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Means, David McGregor (1847-1931), 1880; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Meill, C. A, 1871; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Melani, Alfredo, 1903; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Mercer University, 1918-1919; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Merlini, A, 1902; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Mershon, I. W., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Michel, Andre (1853-1925), 1912-1916; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Miller, William H, 1872-1879; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Milliken, Harry, 1912; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Mills, Lawrence Heyworth (1837-1918), 1888; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Minturn, A. P. S, 1912; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Modigliani, Ettore, 1901; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Moffat, James C. (1811-1890), 1876-1877; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Mommsen, Theodor (1817-1903), 1895; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Moore, George Henry (1823-1892), 1876; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Morey, Charles Rufus (1877-1955), 1903-1922; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Morgan, John Pierpont, Jr. (1867-1943), 1900-1918; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Morgan, Junius Spencer (1867-1932), 1909; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Morgan, Mabelle L, 1911; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Morgan, Sherley W, 1922; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 42)